David E. Lilienthal Papers, 1900-1981 (bulk 1950-1981 ): Inventory MC148
EADs for public policy collection from import batch
- Series 18: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1905 October 19-1981; 208 boxes; 2 items
  - Subseries 18K: 1971-1972, 11 boxes
    - Wilson, Logan, 1971; 1 box (Box 498)
    - Re Acheson, Dean, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Re African American Dialogues, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Ahmadi, Ahmad A, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - American Assembly, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - American Society for Public Administration, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Ansari, Abdol Reza, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Ash, Roy, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Asia Society, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Atchley, Dana W, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Re Atomic Energy, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Bentley, Gerald, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Re Berle, Adolf A, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Bernstein, Marver H, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Bliven, Bruce, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Bohmont., Dale W, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Bowen, William G, 1972; 1 box
      - Re Brazil, 1972; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Amazon River Basin Project, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 499)
    - General, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Sao Francisco Valley Project, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 499)
    - Bromberger, Nancy and Sylvain, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Brooks, John, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Bunting, Mary, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Re Burmah Oil, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Business Week, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Callahan, North, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Case, Josephine Young, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Center for Radiation Tnformation, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Centre D'Etudes Industrielles, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Century Association, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Re China, People's Republic of, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Coates, Albert, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Columbia Journal of World Business, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Cowan, Louis G, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Daniel, Margaret Truman, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Daniels, Tonathan, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Davis, Shelby Cullom, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - de Abreu, Joao L, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Delta-Democrat Times Greenville, RlsgTssippi, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - DePauw University, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Dillon, Douglas, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Re Dominican Republic, 1972; 1 box (Box 500)
    - Ecumenical Institute, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Elliott, Osborn, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Re Energy, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Re Environment, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Evans, Paul L, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Export-Import Bank of the United States, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Fairbank, John K, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Farmanfarmaian, Khodadad, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - First National City Bank, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Flom, Joseph H, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Fugitt, Warren G, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Galantiere, Lewis, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Gandhi, Indira, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Georgetown University - Institute for International and Foreign Trade Law, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Ginzberg, Eli, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Goheen, Robert F, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Goodell, Grace E, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Gottlieb Duttweiler Institute, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Gulhati, N,D, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Hammond Historical Society, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Haynes, William F., Jr, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Hough, Henry B, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Howe, Quincy, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Howland, William S, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Hughes, Emmet J, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Re Indus River Basin, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - International Creative Center, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - International Institute of Environmental Affairs, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Re Iran, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Jesselson, Ludwig, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Johns Hopkins University School of Advanced International Studies, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. - Library: Oral History Interview Re President Johnson by David E. Lilienthal, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Julian, Percy L, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Katzenbach, Nicholas deB, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Knight, Douglas M, 1972; 1 box (Box 501)
    - Re La Follette, Philip, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Langmuir, Alexander, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Lash, Joseph P, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Levy, Walter J, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Licklider, Roy E, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Lilienthal, David E. III, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Lilienthal, Michael, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Littlefield, Edmund W, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - MacMurray College, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Jacksonville, Illinois, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Re Martha's Vineyard, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Martin, Georges-Henri, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Re Martin, Roscoe C, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Meads, Donald E, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Metzger, H. Peter, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Micou, Paul and Ann, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Miller, Lawrence K, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Re Missouri Volley Authority, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Montclair, New Jersey - Adult School, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Morse, David A, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Re Murrow, Edward R. - Center of Public Diplomacy, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Muskie, Edmund S, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Newman, Edwin, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Newsweek, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - New York Times, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Oakes, John B, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Oppenheimer, A Robert, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Memorial Committee, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Overseas Development Council (O.D.C.), 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Penalosa Camargo, Enrique, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Princeton University, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Pritchard, Ross, 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Re Publication by David E. Lilienthal: TVA: Democracy on the March, Portuguese edition., 1972; 1 box (Box 502)
    - Radcliffe College, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Raphaelson, Joel, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Reston, James, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Robinson, William A, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Robock, Stefan H, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Rogers, William P, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Sevareid, Eric, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Seymour, Mrs. Walton, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Sherman, Henry, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Smith, Frank E, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Spivak, Lawrence E, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - State, Department of, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Strauss, Lewis L, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Arthur H, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Szold., Mrs. Bernard, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Szold, Edwin D, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Thames Television, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Thomson of Fleet, Lord, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Tobey, David M, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Tourtellot, Arthur B, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Truman, Harry S. - Library Institute, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Vaughn, Jack H, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Re Vietnam, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Walters, Barbara, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Warne, William E, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Warren, Shields, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Warren, Stafford L, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Webster, Bethuel, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Wells, Herman B, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Wheeler, John A, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Who's Who, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Wiesner, Jerome B, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
    - Wisconsin Senate, 1972; 1 box (Box 503)
  - Subseries 18L: 1973-1974, 12 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence and related material for 1973 and 1974.
    - Abram, Morris B, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Ahmadi, Ahmad A, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - American Assembly, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - American Society for Public Administration, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Anderson, Leo L, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Ansari, Abdol Reza, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Re Armstrong, Hamilton F, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Ash, Roy, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Asia Society, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Atchley, Dana W, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Atlantic Monthly Press, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Baumgartner, Leona, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Berle, Mrs. Adolf, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Biological Conservation, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Bolling, Landrum, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Boston Globe, 1973; 1 box (Box 504)
    - Re Brazil (1 of 2), dates not examined; 1 box
      - Amazon River Basin Project, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 505)
      - Desenvolvimento e Sistemas Company, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 505)
      - General, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 505)
        Includes letters regarding a "Diploma" awarded to David E. Lilienthal by the Brazilian Government
      - Iran Trade, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 505)
    - Re Brazil (2 of 2), dates not examined; 1 box
      - Sao Francisco Valley Project, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 506)
      - Serete Group, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 506)
    - Bromberger, Nancy and Sylvain, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Brooks, John, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Re Burmah Oil, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Burnett, John G, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Byrne, Brendan, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Callahan, North, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Carter, Hodding, III, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Re Carvajal, Manuel, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Century Association, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Chattanooga Engineers Club, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Common Cause, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Davenport, John A, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - de Abreu, Joao L, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Dean, Arthur H, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Dec a tur_Da ily, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - DePauw University, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Doar, John, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Re Energy, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Engineering News Record, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, 1973; 1 box (Box 507)
    - Farmanfarmaian, Khodadad, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - First National City Bank, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Flom, Joseph H, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Forbes Magazine, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Four Freedoms Foundation, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Fugitt, Warren G, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Fulbrightj J. William, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Furnas, J.C., 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Gandhi, Indira, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Greene, Mrs. Nathan, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Greeneye, Mrs. Lawrence, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Hannah, John A, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Harlow, John S, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Harvard Law School, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Harvard University, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Helms, Richard, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Herrera, Felipe, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Hewlett, Richard G, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Hughes, Emmet J, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Re India, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Institute on Man and Science, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - International Bankers' Review, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - International League for the Rights of Man, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Interstate Printers and Publishers, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Iran-America Society, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Julian, Percy L, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Keating, Kenneth B, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Knight, Douglas M, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Re Kriendler, Maxwell A, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lazard Freres and Co. (New York), 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Levy, Walter J, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lilienthal, David E. ITT, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Linen, James A, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lindsay, John V, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Loeb, John N, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Lorentz, Pare, 1973; 1 box (Box 508)
    - Re McKellar, Kenneth D, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Re Maritime Fruit Carriers Company, Ltd, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Martin, Georges-Henri, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Martindell, Anne C, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Miller, Lawrence K, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Morino, Mitsutoshi, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Morse, David A, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Morton (Illinois)High School, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Munoz-Marin, Luis, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - New York Times, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Newsweek, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Oliver, John, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Overseas Development Council (O.D.C.), 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Owen, Marguerite, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Pampanini, Andrea H.A. and Susan, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Penalosa Camargo, Enrique, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Planned Parenthood/World Population, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Praeger Publishers, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Princeton University, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Princeton University Press, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Pritchard, Ross, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Re Publication by David E. Lilienthal: TVA: Democracy on the March. Portuguese edition., 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Re Puerto Rico, 1973; 1 box (Box 509)
    - Rabinowitch, Eugene, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Raphaelson, Joel, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Ray, Dixy Lee, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Reader's Digest, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Reston, James, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Robinson, William J, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Re Rorty, James, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Rosenman, Mrs. Samuel T, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Sen, Sudhir, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Sevareid, Eric, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Seymour, Walton, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Schlesinger, James R, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Schwartz, David, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Smith, Barney and Co, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Smith, Datus C., Jr, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Sorensen, Theodore C, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Southern California, University of (U.S.C.) School of Public Administration, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Szanton, Peter L, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Tehrani, Ahmad, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
      Includes a visit to the Tennessee Valley Authority by Mr. and Mrs. David E. Lilienthal, April 23- 25, 1973
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Truman, Harry S. - Institute, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Re Vietnam, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Volpe, Joseph, Jr, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Webb, James E, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Who's Who, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Re Yale University - Economic Growth Center, 1973; 1 box (Box 510)
    - Re African American Dialogues (programs), 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Ahmadi, Ahmad A, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Aldewereld, Simon, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - American Academy of Arts And Sciences, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - American Society for Public Administration, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Americas Foundation, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Ansari, Abdol Reza, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Asia Society, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Baldwin, Roger N, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Batty, Peter, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Baumgartner, Leona, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Bentley, Gerald, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Billington, James H, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Black, Pamela and Michael, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Blatchford, Joseph H, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Bliven, Bruce, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Bowen, William G, 1974; 1 box
      - Re Brazil, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Desenvolvimento e Sistemas Company, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Sao San Francisco Valley Project, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Bromberger, Nancy and Sylvain, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Brooks, John, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Brown Brothers Harriman & Company, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Bundy, William and Mary, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Business Week, 1974; 1 box (Box 511)
    - Callahan, North, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Carey, Jane C, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Century Association, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Re China, People's Republic of, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Clapp, Norman M, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Committee on Economic Development, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Cooper, Charles A, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Re Cornell, Katharine, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Daggett, John T, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - de Abreu, Joao L, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - de Brantei, Guy, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - De Giacomo, Robert J, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - DePauw University, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Diebold, John, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Dreher, Carl, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Re Emmert, James A, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Emory University, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Re Energy, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Farmanfarmaian, Khodadad, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Ferris, John P, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Flammang, Janet A, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Fortune Magazine, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Four Freedoms Foundation, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Fowler, Henry H, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Friendly, Alfred, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Fugitt, Warren G, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Fulbright, J. WillAm, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Galantiere, Lewis, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - General Electric Company, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - George Washington University, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Ginzberg, Eli, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Goheen, Robert F, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Golden, William T, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - Goodell, Grace E, 1974; 1 box (Box 512)
    - "Granges A.B. Contract", 1974; 1 box
      - (1 of 2), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 513)
      - (2 of 2), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Greene, Mrs. Nathan, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Gremliza, F.G. Louis, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Gridiron Club, Washington, D.C., 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Hamilton, Edward K, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Harvard Law School, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Harvard University, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Heckscher, August, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Heffner, Richard D, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Heiskanen, Piltti, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Re Hoffman, Paul G, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Hough, Henry B, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Howland, William S, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Re Iran, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Jackson, Henry M, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Janeway, Eliot and Elizabeth, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Jesselson, Ludwig, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Jessup, John K, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Jones, Robert E, 1974; 1 box (Box 513)
    - Keating, Kenneth B, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Knight, Douglas M, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lilienthal, David E. III, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lilienthal, Margaret L, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lilienthal, Michael, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Linen, James A, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Linowitz, Sol M, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - McGhee, George C, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - McNeil, Marshall, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Macy, John W., Jr, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Re Martha's Vineyard, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Mendenhall, Tom, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Meras, Phyllis, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Meyer, Ralph H, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Meyner, Helen and Robert, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Morgenthau, Robert M, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Morse, David A, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - Nebraska, University of, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)
    - New York Times, 1974; 1 box (Box 514)